Luis Magana

E-mail: 2017luismagana@gmail.com * GitHub: https://github.com/MaganaLu * Telephone number: +1-509-387-9799

Introduction

A highly motivated software engineer with a diverse background in programming languages. I have technical knowledge with UI/UX design as well as back-end implementation experience through the use of the c# .Net framework. I enjoy learning new technologies and solving problems. I like to learn web development on my free time which I update on my GitHub. I am excited to continue growing as a software developer.

Summary of Qualifications

- C#.Net Windows Presentation Format, Java, TypeScript/JavaScript, HMTL, CSS, Python, SQL
- UI/UX design and development

- Photoshop experience, 3D modeling experience
- Mobile Web Development, Application Development

Work experience

Fives DyAg

Controls Engineer

September 2023 - Present

Seattle, WA

- Worked on different projects both PLC and HMI related.
- Worked with Ignition, Beckhoff, and Siemens

Taqueria El Tarasco - Contract

Web Developer

 $November\ 2023$ - $December\ 2023$

Remote

- Created a responsive restaurant website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript using ReactJs
- Used Photoshop and other tools to create custom Images for overall look and feel of website

Irwin Research and Development

Software Development Engineer

September 2021 - September 2023 Yakima, WA

- Designed and implemented the communication model between Siemens PLC and the C# front-end.
- Multiple Controllers are allowed to connect to the HMI through custom highly reusable libraries that enable the HMI/UI to be used on any factory machine without having the hard coded nature of the PLC limit the flexibility of the HMI. I used C# and Structured text in development.
- Designed and Implemented front-end controls and panels from scratch using Winforms and then transitioned to WPF.

Safilog Logistics - Contract

Software Developer

September 2020 - June 2021

Ellensburg, WA

• Designed and collaborated with a team to complete a logistics mobile app that can connect independent delivery agents, customers, and farmers together to form a farm to market to consumer chain. I implemented the front end and back end capabilities and designed the overall user experience for the users. I used Typescript and CSS to make this project along with SQL in React.

Education

Bachelor's degree in Computer Science

Bachelor's degree program Math Minor Final GPA: 3.1 Central Washington University September 2017 - June 2021